[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "I mean, in all your time in police work, Captain Evans, have you ever come across anything quite so callous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "No, I haven't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Evans"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", ":", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "And final question for you, Captain Evans, just clarify for me, is it right that their explanation was simply that they were bored and they did it for fun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "VANS: You know, I really, as captain of investigations, we have a policy over here that, you know, I can't discuss what anybody's statement is, you know, if anybody discusses that, they are a little bit higher pay grade than me, but -- so I really can't go into the specifics of what any of them said, but one thing I can say about this group is they had the desire to be gangsters.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Evans"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "There's been widespread fury and distress in Australia over this, hasn't there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "There really has.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Australia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1996"], "LOCATION": ["Australia", "United States"]}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "What is your reaction to what has happened here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Just for the record, Australia has had zero gun massacres since 1996 and the United States 80 people killed by guns every single day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["USA", "CNN"], "LOCATION": ["Vietnam"], "PERSON": ["Dick Cheney", "Joe Biden", "John Winston"]}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Let me just ask you, you were in a conservative government, weren't you, Mr. Fischer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Yes, I was leader of the Republican Regional Party equivalent, congressman equivalent, in a sense a Dick Cheney or Joe Biden equivalent, deputy prime minister, and I supported strongly John Winston out, and the initiatives for gun law reform and also former Vietnam veteran thanks to the USA, and I have and own guns, which CNN had footage of, as a matter of fact.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Fischer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "What kind of man was Christopher?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Well, he was this kid that started actually at 7 years old at our club playing tee ball which is, you know, looked like a little league type program.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Did he like the idea of buying into the American dream?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Look, look, Chris was such a level-headed kid that I think he knew his downfalls.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "What do you make of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, you know, what often characterized as juvenile violence is a senseless nature.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "How empowering is the gun to kids like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBG", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Well, very much so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "What do you have to say about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "You know, it breaks my heart that a young man lost his life in such a senseless manner.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", ":", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "What is wrong with the argument in America that makes it so nonsensical?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "It's not a partisan issue, especially when there is a dead kid on the ground or -- or in the ground.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Lee, do you think America is more or less racist country since Barack Obama became president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Wow, that's a powerful question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "What do you think, Star, to that central question of whether Barack Obama's ascent to the White House drew out more racism to America or it was always there and they just made the debate noisier?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "I think people just have a little more freedom to have this discussion and to say some of the things that they would normally not say in polite company.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "LOCATION": ["America"], "PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "-- what was the difference really?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "They didn't throw race.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "``", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 385, "question": "How fast after you pulling him out did it go up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "As we're walking away, I sit him down and he looks at his car and he goes, \"Is that my car on fire?\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Have you heard from Dick Van Dyke?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Van Dyke"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Yes, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "But thank you both very much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["New York City", "Boston"]}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "A Red Sox fan -- Bill, how are you going to pull that off?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "You know, Piers, New York City is a city of immigrants, including immigrants from the Boston area.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Red Sox"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "So why not go with the glass ceiling and go with old Bill?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "I've known Bill for 10-plus years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "The subtle charms of Anthony Weiner haven't -- haven't appealed to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Not so far.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "RBR", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Cynthia, if you were doing a slogan for Bill, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "Bill de Blasio, for a more fairer, more equitable, more just New York.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill"]}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Is it long?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I think I prefer your daughter's line, Bill.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130820pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Not a boring white guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Yes, I think that's the best tag line I've ever heard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]